so we have seen that the duplication of
all the register values that have all
ever been produced is a problem uh so we
will look at registry naming which is
another scheme that uh can provide uh
relief from false dependencies but in a
way that actually is more manageable how
does the register naming work so
registry naming separates the concept of
architectural registers which are the
registers that the programmers and the
compilers use so this is when you write
an instruction like add R1 R2 R3 the R1
R2 and R3 that you're referring to are
the architectural registers in register
naming there is also a concept of
physical registers which is all the
places that we can actually put a value
in the processor so there is of course a
place for kind of the latest value of R1
for example but there could be
additional places where we could
potentially store values that should be
going to R1 and then what we do is as
the processor reads instructions and
figures out which registers they they're
using and remember the program is
referring to architecture registers as
it's fetching instructions and decoding
them it also does registry naming which
pretty much means that it rewrites the
program to use the physical registers so
basically if it sees add R1 R2 R3 it's
going to rename That Into You Know add R
something else and so on in order to
basically refer to the places where it
has actually put those values and how
does it know where the values are
well it uses a table called register
allocation table or rat and you should
remember this because we will be very
frequently referring to the rat because
it's used very very often what the rat
is is a table that says which physical
registers has the value for which
architecture register so for each of the
architecture registers there will be an
entry in this table and it will say what
is the current location in the physical
registers where the value for that
architectural registers can be found